Now, there's not just React;
Teraz nie tylko
there are also alternatives. React, of course, is what we'll cover in this course.
React; s te alternatywy. Reakcja jest oczywicie tym, co omwimy na tym kursie.
There is also Angular and Vue.js as well as others like Backbone and Ember, but
Istnieje rwnie Angular i Vue. js, a take inne, takie jak Backbone i
Angular and Vue are the most popular alternatives.
Ember, ale Angular i Vue s najpopularniejszymi alternatywami.
I can only recommend diving into these two to really pick your favorite.
Mog tylko poleci nurkowanie w tych dwch, aby naprawd wybra ulubionego.
I've also got courses on them if you're interested.
Mam te kursy na ich temat, jeli jeste zainteresowany.
All three of them are great at creating highly-scalable web applications that look and feel good to
Wszystkie trzy s wietne w tworzeniu wysoce skalowalnych aplikacji internetowych, ktre wygldaj i dobrze si
the user.
czuj dla uytkownika.
Not so much an alternative is jQuery; where he you might think it is, but jQuery is really only about
Nie tyle alternatyw jest jQuery; gdzie on moe si wydawa, e tak jest, ale jQuery w rzeczywistoci chodzi tylko
traversing the DOM and targeting elements in the DOM.
o przechodzenie przez DOM i targetowanie elementw w DOM.
Now, as you saw in our example, React is about just declaring what you see and focusing on the logic
Teraz, jak widzielimy w naszym przykadzie, React polega wanie na zadeklarowaniu tego, co widzisz i skupieniu
instead of focusing on the 'how'. Therefore, React, Angular and Vue allow you to create more powerful
si na logice, zamiast skupia si na "jak". Dlatego React, Angular i Vue pozwalaj tworzy bardziej
applications because you can focus on the logic and your business model and not so much on the technical
zaawansowane aplikacje, poniewa mona skupi si na logice i modelu biznesowym, a nie na technicznej
side of actually reaching an element
stronie faktycznego dotarcia do elementu, ktry
you want to change.
chcesz zmieni.